Let's revisit the cylinder volume function,
لنعد إلى دالة حجم الأسطوانة،
but with one modification.
لكن مع تعديل واحد.
This function includes a default argument.
تحتوي هذه الدالة على وسيطة افتراضية.
If radius is not specified,
إذا لم يتم تحديد نصف القطر،
then the variable radius will default to five when used in the function body.
فسيحمل المتغيّر radius القيمة الافتراضية 5 عند استخدامه في كتلة الدالة.
Calling the function like this would be the same thing as calling it like this,
استدعاء الدالة بهذا الشكل هو تماماً كاستدعائها هكذا،
because radius is set to five if not specified as another value.
لأن radius سيحمل القيمة 5 في حال لم يتم تحديد قيمة أخرى له.
Default arguments allow functions to use default values when those arguments are omitted.
الوسيطات الافتراضية تسمح للدوال باستخدام القيم الافتراضية عند حذف هذه الوسيطات.
This is helpful because it can make your code more concise in
هذا مفيد لأن بإمكانه جعل الكود مختصراً أكثر
scenarios where there is a common value you can use for a variable,
في الحالات حيث توجد قيمة مشتركة يمكن استخدامها لمتغيّر ما،
although you still want it to be customizable.
لكن لا تزال ترغب بأن يكون قابلاً للتعديل.
In this example, the default radius is five but we can still change this.
في هذا المثال، نصف القطر الافتراضي هو 5 لكن لا يزال بإمكاننا تغيير هذا.
This time when we call the function,
عندما نستدعي الدالة هذه المرة،
we are overriding the default value of five and calculating
فإننا نتجاوز القيمة الافتراضية، أي 5،
Also notice here, we're passing values to our arguments by position.
لاحظوا أيضاً أننا نقوم هنا بتمرير قيم إلى وسيطاتنا بحسب الموقع.
It's possible to pass values in two ways,
من الممكن تمرير القيم بطريقتين،
by position and by name.
حسب الموقع أو حسب الاسم.
Each of these function is evaluated in the same way.
يتم تقييم كل واحدة من هذه الدوال بالطريقة ذاتها.
This one is simply taking the arguments by
تأخذ هذه الدالة الوسيطات بحسب الموقع ببساطة،
There are some nuances for when you can perform
توجد بعض الفروق الصغيرة في متى يمكنكم تنفيذ
the passing of values in each of these ways.
تمرير القيم في كل واحدة من هاتين الطريقتين.
You'll see more applications of this in the following quiz section.
ستتعرفون على المزيد من التطبيقات على هذا في قسم الاختبار التالي.